If you have something to say, just say it.
What's going on between you two?
If this is posted online,
what do you think
would happen to Jung Yihyun?
Oh.
Jung Yihyun...
Since he's a celebrity,
I just hung out with him a few times.
He's actually pretty boring.
What are you doing?
[Hongseok]
[Park Seonghyeon]
[Shin Yongseok] [Shin Junseop] [Ha Yosep]
[Play Me]
Hey!
You really wore it.
You told me to wear it.
Thanks for preparing this for me.
It suits you.
You too.
Let's go then.
Okay.
Woah!
See that?
Not bad.
Oh, it's the security guard!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Do you remember?
[Here are the photos you asked for.]
This is all for Yihyun's own good.
[How about reporting a scandal
on the top star Jung Yihyun?]
[Reporter Park Siwan]
It's killing me, rehearsing every day.
Emergency! Emergency!
[Musical "The Mermaid Prince"
is sold out!]
We're
sold out!
Oh?
What's wrong? Why are you blushing?
Wait, why are you suddenly coughing—
We'll get going.
Take care.
Oh, it's a taxi!
Bye.
I'll get going too.
Wanna
have dinner together?
My treat.
Did they have a fight?
They did look upset.
Guess I was just being paranoid.
Wanna go on a date?
How about a cafe?
It's a nice day. Let's go for a walk.
Uh... I forgot I have something to do.
I've to go.
Why did you suddenly ask to meet?
I received this.
[How about reporting a scandal
on the top star Jung Yihyun?]
What the hell?
Someone sent these in,
asking me to expose Jung Yihyun's scandal.
Expose his scandal?
Don't worry, I won't write about it.
I refused, saying I didn't want to
harass a retired actor.
If this is posted online,
what do you think
would happen to Jung Yihyun?
What are you plotting?
Didn't you threaten me with this before?
Back then...
I'm sorry.
I couldn't control my feelings for you,
so I did something I shouldn't have.
It's ridiculous to say this now,
but you and Jung Yihyun drifted apart
because of me.
I'm sorry.
What?
The day I threatened you...
Jung Yihyun saw us.
So I did that on purpose.
Eden's never reassured Luka.
How could Luka be certain?
If you love someone,
you must find the courage...
Even when he might be betrayed?
So...
that's why he...
Be careful.
You might be fine,
but Jung Yihyun could lose everything.
Let's talk.
Be careful.
You might be fine,
but Jung Yihyun could lose everything.
You're a bit late.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine.
But you don't look so good.
I'm really fine.
Let's go to the hospital...
Just leave me alone
for a while.
I'm sorry.
Let's call it a day.
Good work, guys.
I'll head back.
H-Hang on!
Um, well...
How about we...
go on a trip together?
What do you say?
The premiere's coming up.
It's a good time to relax
and do some team building.
S-Sounds awesome.
I'm in!
Uh,
I...
Agreed.
I think we've rehearsed enough.
Let's set off tomorrow.
-Yes!
You'll join us, right?
I guess.
Wow, the air is so fresh.
I heard there's a really good
scallion pancake place nearby.
How about some scallion pancakes
and rice wine after the hike?
Answer me!
My mouth's watering already.
Come on, let's go!
You've been looking down since yesterday.
Is something wrong?
Uh, um...
It's nothing.
Okay.
If you have anything to say,
you can tell me anytime.
I'll wait for you.
Wait a minute.
It seems faster to go that way.
Jae-on,
wanna go scout the path with me?
Yeah, sure.
[Restricted Area; Keep Out]
But...
I don't think this way is it.
Jae-on!
Hold on. I have a call.
I'll be right back.
Hey...
Mr. Yoo told me to make sure
Jae-on misses the performance.
Is this really right?
Hey.
Wake up.
Kang Jae-on,
don't mess with me, okay?
I'm fine!
Got you.
Don't joke about things like this.
Where are you going?
Are you okay?
Argh...
I played it off only because
I didn't want him to worry.
I should just tell him everything.
Was that something to joke about?
But he seemed really hurt.
Do you remember?
When you were suffering
from a career slump,
we used to drink beer
by Han River every night.
I was really grateful for that.
Thanks to you,
I could take a breather.
I...
always felt sorry for you.
You had to be a good son and a good actor,
always trying to
meet others' expectations.
You looked really miserable.
So I hoped that at least
when you were with me,
you could smile without a care.
Maybe, it was from then on
that I fell for you.
Yihyun,
let's go live in the US together
after this musical ends.
I'll treat you even better.
You won't have to do anything.
I appreciate it,
but I want to keep doing musicals.
Is it because of Kang Jae-on?
Who has always been by your side
and helped you when you broke down?
It was me, not Kang Jae-on!
I know very well
how much you've looked out for me.
I do.
But the one I love is Jae-on.
Do you think
he'll stay by your side forever?
Jae-on...
Since he's a celebrity,
I just hung out with him a few times.
Let's go to the hospital...
You've been looking down since yesterday.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
I'm the only one
who will love you forever.
You know that too, don't you?